[
      {
           "question": "What is the maximum possible length of the identifier?",
           "options":
           [
                 "A. 31 characters",
                 "B. 63 characters",
                 "C. 79 characters",
                 "D. None of the above"
           ],
           "answer": "D. None of the above"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which of the following is invalid?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. _a = 1",
                  "B. __a = 1",
                  "C. _str_ = 1",
                  "D. None of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "D. None of the above"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a keyword?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. eval",
                  "B. assert",
                  "C. nonlocal",
                  "D. pass"
            ],
            "answer": "A. eval"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which of the following is an invalid statement?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. abc = 1000000",
                  "B. a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
                  "C. a,b,c = 1000,2000,3000",
                  "D. a_b_c = 1000000"
            ],
            "answer": "B. a b c = 1000 2000 3000"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which of the following cannot be a variable?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. _init_",
                  "B. in",
                  "C. it",
                  "D. on"
            ],
            "answer": "B. in"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which is the correct operator for power(x) of y?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. x ^ y",
                  "B. x ** y",
                  "C. x ^^ y",
                  "D. None of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "B. x ** y"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which one of these is a floor division?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. /",
                  "B. //",
                  "C. %",
                  "D. None of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "B. //"
      },
      {
            "question": "What is the answer of the expresion, 22 % 3 is?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. 5",
                  "B. 0",
                  "C. 7",
                  "D. 1"
            ],
            "answer": "D. 1"
      },
      {
            "question": "Operator with the same precedence are evaluated in which manner?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Left to Right",
                  "B. None of the mentioned",
                  "C. Can't say",
                  "D. Right to Left"
            ],
            "answer": "A. Left to Right"
      },
      {
            "question": "What is the output of the expresion, 3*1**3?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. 27",
                  "B. 6",
                  "C. 3",
                  "D. 1"
            ],
            "answer": "C. 3"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which of the following has highest precedence in the expresion?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Parantheses",
                  "B. Addtion",
                  "C. Exponential",
                  "D. Multiplication"
            ],
            "answer": "A. Parantheses"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which of these is not a core data type?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Dictionary",
                  "B. Lists",
                  "C. Class",
                  "D. Tuples"
            ],
            "answer": "C. Class"
      },
      {
            "question": "Given a function that does not return any value, what value is thrown by default when executed in shell?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Int",
                  "B. bool",
                  "C. void",
                  "D. None"
            ],
            "answer": "D. None"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which of the following will run without errors?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. round(45.8)",
                  "B. round(6352.898,2.5)",
                  "C. round()",
                  "D. round(7465.33,2,1)"
            ],
            "answer": "A. round(45.8)"
      },
      {
            "question": "In order to store values in terms of keys and value we use what core data type?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. list",
                  "B. dictionary",
                  "C. tuple",
                  "D. class"
            ],
            "answer": "B. dictionary"
      },
      {
            "question": "What is the output of the print 0.1 + 0.2 == 0.3?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. True",
                  "B. False",
                  "C. Machine Dependent",
                  "D. Error"
            ],
            "answer": "B. False"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a complex number?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. K = 2 + 3j",
                  "B. K = complex(2.3)",
                  "C. K = 2 + 3i",
                  "D. K = 2 + 3J"
            ],
            "answer": "C. K = 2 + 3i"
      },
      {
            "question": "What is type of inf?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. boolean",
                  "B. integer",
                  "C. float",
                  "D. complex"
            ],
            "answer": "C. float"
      },
      {
            "question": "What does ~4 evaluate to?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. -5",
                  "B. -4",
                  "C. -3",
                  "D. +3"
            ],
            "answer": "A. -5"
      },
      {
            "question": "What is the result of round(0.5) - round(-0.5)?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. 1.0",
                  "B. 2.0",
                  "C. 0.0",
                  "D. Value depend upon python version"
            ],
            "answer": "D. Value depend upon python version"
      },
      {
            "question": "What does 3 ^ 4 evaluate to?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. 81",
                  "B. 12",
                  "C. 0.75",
                  "D. 7"
            ],
            "answer": "D. 7"
      }
]